<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<playscript title="The FBI's Most Unwanted">
    <characters>
        <character name="MULDER"/>
        <character name="SCULLY"/>
    </characters>

    <knot id="start" divert="qualifications">
        <line character="MULDER">Sorry, nobody down here but the FBI's most unwanted.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Agent Mulder. I'm Dana Scully, I've been assigned to work with you.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Oh, isn't it nice to be suddenly so highly regarded? So, who did you tick off to get stuck with this detail, Scully?</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Actually, I'm looking forward to working with you. I've heard a lot about you.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Oh, really? I was under the impression...</line>
        <choices character="MULDER">
            <choice>that you were sent to spy on me.</choice>
            <choice bomb="1">that you and the other Agents like to make fun of me.</choice>
            <choice bomb="2">... damn it, I lost my train of thought there.</choice>
        </choices>
    </knot>

    <knot id="qualifications" divert="physics">
        <line character="SCULLY">If you have any doubt about my qualifications or credentials, th...</line>
        <line character="MULDER">You're a medical doctor, you teach at the academy. You did your undergraduate degree in physics.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">"Einstein's Twin Paradox, A New Interpretation. Dana Scully Senior Thesis". Now that's a credential, rewriting Einstein.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Did you bother to read it?</line>
        <choices character="MULDER">
            <choice>I did. I liked it.</choice>
            <choice bomb="2">I prefer the late night cable version.</choice>
            <choice bomb="1">I only read the box scores.</choice>
        </choices>
    </knot>

    <knot id="physics" divert="sturgis">
        <line character="MULDER">It's just that in most of my work, the laws of physics rarely seems to apply.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Maybe I can get your medical opinion on this, though.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Oregon female, age twenty-one, no explainable cause of death. Autopsy shows nothing. Zip.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">There are, however, these two distinct marks on her lower back. Doctor Scully, can you ID these marks?</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Needle punctures, maybe. An animal bite. Electrocution of some kind.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">How's your chemistry? This is the substance found in the surrounding tissue.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">It's organic. I don't know, is it some kind of synthetic protein?</line>
        <choices character="MULDER">
            <choice>Beats me, I've never seen it before either.</choice>
            <choice bomb="2">For all I know it's proof that the King lives.</choice>
            <choice bomb="1" divert="swampgas">The substance may have been swamp gas.</choice>
        </choices>
    </knot>

    <knot id="swampgas" divert="sturgis">
        <line character="SCULLY">Swamp gas?</line>
        <line character="MULDER">It's a natural phenonemon.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Happens to me when I eat Dodger Dogs.</line>
    </knot>

    <knot id="sturgis" divert="unexplained">
        <line character="MULDER">But here it is again in Sturgis, South Dakota.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">And again in Shamrock, Texas.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Do you have a theory?</line>
        <choices character="MULDER">
            <choice>I have plenty of theories.</choice>
            <choice bomb="2" divert="didyoudoit">DID YOU DO IT!?</choice>
            <choice bomb="1" divert = "bunnies">It could be bunnies.</choice>
        </choices>
    </knot>

    <knot id="didyoudoit" divert="unexplained">
        <line character="SCULLY">Mulder?</line>
    </knot>

    <knot id="bunnies" divert="unexplained">
        <line character="SCULLY">I've got a ...</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Bunnies aren't just cute like everybody supposes.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">...</line>
    </knot>

    <knot id="unexplained" divert="obviously-died">
        <line character="MULDER">Maybe what you can explain to me is why it's bureau policy to label these cases as "unexplained phenomenon" and ignore them.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Do you believe in the existence of extraterrestrials?</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Logically, I would have to say "no".</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">Given the distances needed to travel from the far reaches of space, the energy requirements would exceed a spacecraft's capabilities th...</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Conventional wisdom.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">You know this Oregon female? She's the fourth person in her graduating class to die under mysterious circumstances.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">Now, when convention and science offer us no answers...</line>
        <choices character="MULDER">
            <choice>might we not finally turn to the fantastic as a plausibility?</choice>
            <choice bomb="2">maybe we should just give up?</choice>
            <choice bomb="1">might we not find the answers online?</choice>
        </choices>
    </knot>

    <knot id="obviously-died">
        <line character="SCULLY">The girl obviously died of something. If it was natural causes, it's plausible that there was something missed in the post-mortem. If she was murdered, it's plausible there was a sloppy investigation.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">What I find fantastic is any notion that there are answers beyond the realm of science. The answers are there. You just have to know where to look.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">That's why they put the "I" in "F.B.I". See you tomorrow morning, Scully, bright and early.</line>
        <line character="MULDER">We leave for the very plausible state of Oregon at eight A.M.</line>
    </knot>

    <knot id="bomb" threshold="5">
        <line character="SCULLY">Sure, fine, whatever.</line>
        <line character="SCULLY">I'm making like the truth and getting out of here.</line>
    </knot>
</playscript>
